<ServerManagerConfiguration>
  <ProxyGroup name="filters">
    <SourceProxy name="SHYXDeleteSelectedCellsFilter"
                 class="vtkSHYXDeleteSelectedCellsFilter"
                 label="SHYX Delete Selected Cells">
      <Documentation
          long_help="Applies to any vtkDataSet; the output is the same concrete type as the input. Cells included in the active selection (vtkSelection on the Selection port) are removed from vtkPolyData (unused points stripped) and vtkUnstructuredGrid (cell subset), using the same resolution rules as SHYX Selection Extrude (vtkExtractSelection: vtkOriginalCellIds on extracted cells, or vtkOriginalPointIds with all incident cells). For vtkStructuredGrid and vtkExplicitStructuredGrid, selected cells are blanked (BlankCell). For vtkImageData, vtkRectilinearGrid, and other vtkDataSet types, selected cells are hidden using the cell ghost HIDDENCELL bit (topology unchanged). With the VESPA ParaView plugin, the Selection port can be filled from the active selection when you open the filter panel. If there is no vtkSelection, set Selection Cell Array Name on cell data of the input. When nothing is selected, the filter passes the input through unchanged."
          short_help="Delete or hide selected cells on any vtkDataSet (output type matches input)."/>

      <InputProperty name="Input" command="SetInputConnection">
        <ProxyGroupDomain name="groups">
          <Group name="sources"/>
          <Group name="filters"/>
        </ProxyGroupDomain>
        <DataTypeDomain name="input_type">
          <DataType value="vtkDataSet"/>
        </DataTypeDomain>
        <Documentation>
          Any vtkDataSet (output matches input). PolyData and unstructured grids lose cells; structured types use blanking/ghost hiding.
        </Documentation>
      </InputProperty>

      <InputProperty name="Selection" label="Selection"
                     command="SetSourceConnection">
        <ProxyGroupDomain name="groups">
          <Group name="sources"/>
          <Group name="filters"/>
        </ProxyGroupDomain>
        <DataTypeDomain name="input_type">
          <DataType value="vtkSelection"/>
        </DataTypeDomain>
        <Documentation>
          vtkSelection describing cells or points to remove (same convention as SHYX Selection Extrude).
        </Documentation>
        <Hints>
          <SelectionInput/>
        </Hints>
      </InputProperty>

      <StringVectorProperty name="SelectionCellArrayName" label="Selection Cell Array Name"
          command="SetSelectionCellArrayName" number_of_elements="1" default_values="">
        <Documentation>
          If Selection is empty: name of a cell data array on Input. Cells are removed when value &gt; 0.5 (float) or non-zero (integer types).
        </Documentation>
      </StringVectorProperty>

      <Hints>
        <ShowInMenu category="SHYX" icon=":/VESPA/SHYX_Surface_to_Volume_Mesh.png"/>
      </Hints>
    </SourceProxy>
  </ProxyGroup>
</ServerManagerConfiguration>
