<ServerManagerConfiguration>
  <ProxyGroup name="filters">
    <SourceProxy name="SHYXDataSetToPartitionedCollection"
                 class="vtkSHYXDataSetToPartitionedCollection"
                 label="SHYX DataSet To Partitioned Collection">
      <Documentation
          short_help="Split dataset into tet volume, then node sets, then side sets; optional full boundary surface output."
          long_help="Tetrahedra (if any) are extracted first under vtkDataAssembly IOSS/element_blocks/tetrahedra with contiguous GlobalIds (1..N) for IOSS writers. PartitionedDataSetCollection block order is then all node{i} blocks (node_sets), then all side{i} blocks (side_sets). When Partition Point Array Name is set on the extracted boundary vtkPolyData, vtkThreshold with THRESHOLD_BETWEEN (endpoints inclusive in VTK; All Scalars off: any corner qualifies) keeps cells whose first component lies in (-inf, 0]; vtkGeometryFilter and vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter plus vtkAppendPolyData merge all such connected components into one side/node pair if non-empty. A second vtkThreshold pass (also any corner, BETWEEN) keeps first component in [1, +inf); vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter splits that sub-mesh into n connected regions, each its own side/node pair. A cell whose corners all lie strictly in (0, 1) may belong to neither pass. Patch order is the merged non-positive patch first (if present), then the n patches at or above 1 (up to n+1 pairs). If the array is missing or the wrong length, or the name is cleared, or both passes yield no cells, the full surface is split with vtkPolyDataNormals (Feature Angle) and vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter instead. Sort By Area and Custom Post Reorder apply to the full list of patches. Block metadata sets NAME and vtkIOSSReader ENTITY_ID. Output port 1 is the full boundary vtkPolyData before sign-splitting."/>

      <OutputPort name="Partitioned collection" index="0" id="port0"/>
      <OutputPort name="Boundary surface (pre-split)" index="1" id="port1"/>

      <InputProperty name="Input" command="SetInputConnection">
        <ProxyGroupDomain name="groups">
          <Group name="sources"/>
          <Group name="filters"/>
        </ProxyGroupDomain>
        <DataTypeDomain name="input_type">
          <DataType value="vtkDataSet"/>
        </DataTypeDomain>
      </InputProperty>

      <StringVectorProperty name="PartitionPointArrayName" label="Partition Point Array Name"
          command="SetPartitionPointArrayName" number_of_elements="1" default_values="EndpointIndex">
        <Documentation>
          Point-data array on the boundary: first vtkThreshold first component in (-inf, 0] with THRESHOLD_BETWEEN (inclusive endpoints; any corner),
          merged to one patch; then [1, +inf) (any corner), split by vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter
          into n patches (up to n+1 side/node pairs). Default EndpointIndex. Clear to use Feature angle /
          vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter on the full surface only.
        </Documentation>
      </StringVectorProperty>

      <DoubleVectorProperty name="FeatureAngle" label="Feature angle (deg)" command="SetFeatureAngle"
          number_of_elements="1" default_values="70.0" animateable="0">
        <DoubleRangeDomain name="range" min="0.0" max="180.0"/>
        <Documentation>
          Used when Partition Point Array Name is empty, or the named array is missing / wrong length, or
          sign-split threshold yields no patches: vtkPolyDataNormals dihedral threshold for cusp / sharp
          edge split, then vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter regions. Larger values merge more smooth neighborhoods.
        </Documentation>
      </DoubleVectorProperty>

      <IntVectorProperty name="SortByArea" label="Sort By Area" command="SetSortByArea"
          number_of_elements="1" default_values="1" animateable="0">
        <BooleanDomain name="bool"/>
        <Documentation>
          When enabled (default), reorder all node{i} and side{i} patches by total surface area of each side patch, largest first. When disabled, patch order follows the sign-split construction order (merged &lt;=0 region first, then &gt;=1 connectivity regions), or vtkPolyDataConnectivityFilter region indices on the feature-angle fallback path.
        </Documentation>
      </IntVectorProperty>

      <IntVectorProperty name="CustomPostReorder" label="Custom Post Reorder" command="SetCustomPostReorder"
          number_of_elements="1" default_values="1" animateable="0">
        <BooleanDomain name="bool"/>
        <Documentation>
          When enabled (default), after the current patch order is fixed (e.g. by Sort By Area), move the third patch to the first position and the first patch to the last position. The second patch follows the new first, then the original fourth through (n-1) in order. No effect if there are fewer than three patches.
        </Documentation>
      </IntVectorProperty>

      <Hints>
        <ShowInMenu category="SHYX" icon=":/VESPA/SHYX_DataSet_To_Partitioned_Collection.png"/>
        <RepresentationType view="RenderView" type="Surface" port="1"/>
      </Hints>
    </SourceProxy>
  </ProxyGroup>
</ServerManagerConfiguration>
